Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection 1955-1988 MSS 116 MSS.116
Fales Library and Special Collections
- First Accretion
  - RAM-10. #108. Cannon, Tony: Mountain Stud. (Hamilton House), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - RAM-10. #109. Edwards, Mark: Cherry Cop. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - RAM-10. #110. Milano, Chris: Brawny. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - RAM-10. #111. Stuart, Chad: The Meat Eaters. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - RAM-10. #112. Mark, Julian: Special Duty. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - RAM-10. #113. Stuart, Chard: Buck. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - RAM-10. #115. Cannon, Tony: Hustler. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - RAM-10. #116. Mark, Julian: Jump Squad. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - RAM-10. #117. Ward, Roger: Holler Uncle. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - RAM-10. #118. Baldwin, Dick: Naked Danger. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - RAM-10. #119. Stuart, Chad: A Presidential Affair. (Hamilton House), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Rapture Books 408. Culver, Ed: Kept Boy. (Rapture), 1964 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Regency 1026. Tressner, William B: Queens of the Quarter. (Regency), 1970 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Roadhouse Classics 101. Evans, Jack: Blackie. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Roadhouse Classics 102. Proffers, J.J: Hey There Orgy Boy. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Roadhouse Classics 104. Evans, Jack: Stage Stud. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Roadhouse Classics 111. Proffers, J.J: Barracks Orgy. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Roadhouse Classics 116. Evans, Jack: Buzzy. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Roadhouse Classics. Dandridge, Guy: Gay Patrolman. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Roadhouse Classics 122. Dandridge, Guy: Ready, Willing, and Able. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Roadhouse Classics 123. Proffers, J.J: Swap Out. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Roadhouse Classics 124. Short, Roger: Stud On the Rocks. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Rough Trade 401. Ferren, George: Miami Hustler. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061152 0
  - Rough Trade 410.Lawrence, Floyd: Slave Boy. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Rough Trade 413. Marcus, James: Rough Trade. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Rough Trade 415. Wilson,George: Ten Time Hole. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Rough Trade 417. Minor, Jack: Pumping Rookie. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Rough Trade 419. Lawrence, Floyd: The Cocky Repairman. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rough Trade 426. Rulen, Brad: Teenage Rider. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Rough Trade 428. Eberhard, Paul: Road Gang. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rough Trade 433. Proctor, Harry: Dirt Bike Orgy. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Rough Trade 436. Glenn, David: Highway Humpers. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Rough Trade 437. Davies, John: Leather Bound and Beaten. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Rough Trade 438. Spear, Charles: Hot White Suckers. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Rough Trade 439. Darren, Jason: Trucking Sucker. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Rough Trade 441. Cooper, Bill: Boot Licker. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Rough Trade 443. Spears, Charles: Hot, Hard Comers. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Rough Trade 444. Baron, Milt: Hard Truckin' Sucker. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Rough Trade 446. Bart, L.K: Backdoor Slave. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Rough Trade 447. Courage, Kevin: Hard, Horny Cowpokes. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Rough Trade 448. Courage, Kevin: Man Handled Men. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Rough Trade 449. Hall, Marnie: Underage Dick. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Rough Trade 450. Rig, Lance: Texas Gang Rape. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Rough Trade 451. Hall, Marnie: First Rape. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Rough Trade 452. Newman, Alan: Glory Hole. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Rough Trade 454. Lynch, Dick: Hard Behind Bars. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Rough Trade 457. Wood, Spike: Fist Master. (s.l.), undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Rough Trade 458. Rogers, L.K: Cock Strip. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061153 8
  - Rough Trade 459. Hall, Mannie: Brownout Bait. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Rough Trade 460. Harden, Eric: Motorcycle Cops. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Rough Trade 466. Luger, Kurt: Berlin Buddies. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Rough Trade 468. Hall, Mannie: Hot Cocky Cowboy. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Rough Trade 469. Greene, D.C: Midnight Cowboy. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Rough Trade 470. Avery, Everett: Road Boys. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Rough Trade 472. Moro, Martin: King of the Docks. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Rough Trade 479. Narr, Martin: Rough Rider. (s.l.), undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Rough Trade 488. Anonymous: Stable Boy. (Star Distributors), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Rough Trade 492. Anonymous: Marine Master. (Star Distributors), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Rough Trade 497. Anonymous: Brutal Seaman. (Star Distributors), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Signet E8660. Spada, James: The Spada Report- The Newest Survey of Gay Male Sexuality. (Spada), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Signet E9970. Hamilton, Wallace: Kevin. (Hamilton), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Signet J9345. Oster, Jerry: Port Wine Stain. (Oster), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Sir Velvet Press 105. McHenry, David: Hot Nights and Damp Sheets. (Valley Circle Publishing), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Sir Velvet Press 109. Moute, Alex: The Rough Trade. (Valley Circle), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Softcover Library B825X. Thompson, John B: The Lash. (Softcover Library), 1965 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Softcover Library 936X. Burke, Fern: The Jebson Twins. (Softcover), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Spade Classics 101. Lloyd, Chuck: The Gang Rape. (Star Distributors), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Spade Classics 102. Lyons, Jack: Ten-Inch Lover. (Spade Classics), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Spade Classics 103. Taylor, Shad: The Master Cowboy. (Star Distributors), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Spade Classics 104. Cassidy, Will: Locker Room Buddies. (Star Distributors), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Spade Classics 106. Roman, Mark: Hardon Beach. (Star Distributors), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061154 6
  - Spade Classics 107. Ryan, Shad: Ass Hole Buddies. (Star Distributors), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Spade Classics 118. Pichette, Roland: Cycle Slaves. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Spade Classics 125. West, Jim: The Father Affair. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Spade Classics 126. Champion, Mitchell: The Love Rammers. (Star), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Spade Classics 127. Stevenson, Paul: Pretty Boy Lifeguard. (Star), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Spade Classics 128. Cassidy, Will: The Blue-Eyed Stud. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Spade Classics 130. Styles, Lee: The Gay Whores. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Spade Classics 131. Schaeffer, Parker: Hank's Navy Buddies. (Star), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Spade Publishing 134. Dwight, Harrison: Three Is A Lucky Number. (Spade), undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Spade Publishing Inc. Bone, I. L: Boy Whore. (Spade Publishing), undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Spartan Classics 110. Lewis, Mike: Love In A Steam Bath. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Love, James: Square Queer. [Full Color Illustrations]. (s.l.), undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Stud Series 1006. Reed, Lance: Rough Boys In Denim. (Star Distributors), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Stud Series 1011. Gaellis, Jackson: Uniformed Rape. (Star Distributors), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Stud Series 1014. Riggins, Mitchell: Firehouse Rookie. (Star Distributors), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Stud Series 1015. Dukes, Roger: Gridiron Meat. (Star Distributors), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Stud Series 1018. Jones, Dillard: Manhandled. (Star Distributors), 1976 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Stud Series 1019. Wood, H, C: Street Punk. (Star Distributors), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Stud Series 1026. Bryan, Dan: Trucker Stop. (Star Distributors), 1979 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Sundown Reader 602. Holliday, Don: The Gay Trap. (Sundown Reader), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Sundown Reader 605. Dexter, John: The Gay Ones. (Sundown Reader), 1966 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Supreme Library 516. Morton, Herb: Gay and Happy. (Paramount), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061155 3
  - Svea Book 62. Llewellyn, Terry: Homosexual Love Letters. (Nordisk Bladcentral), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Taurus Publication 225. King, Bruce: Leather Boy. (Taurus), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Marcus, James: Tender Butt. (w.l.), undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Sweeney, Gunther: Tight Teenagers.[Illustrated]. (w.l.), undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Torch Reader 1031. Duncan, Rodney: Lots of Action. (Torch Reader), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Tower Book 45-182. Hastings, March: The Boys and Brigham Lee. (Tower), undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 63. Talsman, William: The Gaudy Image [British Edition],. (Olympia Press), 1958 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 103. Homer and Associates: A Bedtime Odyssey [British Edition],. (Olympia Press), 1966 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 205. Richardson, Humphrey: The Sexual Life of Robinson Crusoe. (Olympia Press), 1962; 1967 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Traveler's Companion 206. Homer and Associates: A Bedside Odyssey. Trans. Gerald Williams. (Traveler's Companion), 1956; 1967 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 211. Barrows, Philip: Whores, Queers, and Others, Volume I. (Traveler's Companion), 1967 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 302. Talsman, William: The Gaudy Image. (Traveler's Companion), 1958 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Traveler's Companion Series 465. D'Archangelo, Angelo: Sookey. (Traveler's Companion), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Traveler's Companion Series. Jay, Victor: The Gay Haunt. (Traveler's Companion), 1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Traveler's Companion 507. Marsh, Jon: Mad About A Boy. (Traveler's Companion), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Traveler's Companion 508. Flinders, Carl: Up Daddy, A Love Story. (Traveler's Companion), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Traveler's Companion 509. Ebbing, I.V: Sherbet and Sodomy. (Traveler's Companion), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Traveler's Companion 510. Amory, Richard: Frost. (Traveler's Companion), 1971 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Triumph Fiction Book 312. Mitchell, Carl: Walk The Gay Night. (Triumph), 1967 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Triumph Novel 316. Farr, Kelton: His Secret Life. (Triumph), 1968 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Triumph News Company 327. Allyson, Kim: Mansion of Men. (Triumph), 1968 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Trojan Classic 201. Tulane, Rick: Over Eighteen Over Eight. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061156 1
  - Trojan Classic 208. Temple, Dal: T-Town Tease. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Trojan Classic 220. Tulane, Rick: His Brother's Keeper. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Trojan Classic 222. Temple, Dal: Hung Overly. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Trojan Classic 223. Everts, Tag: The Jock Pot/Book II. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Trojan Classic 225. Everts, Tag: Pay Twenty One. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Trojan Classic 229. Everts, Tag: Come Nine. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Trojan Classic 234. Everts, Tag: Heads Are Winners. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Trojan Classic 236. Lawrence, Ross: The Groovy Juvies. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Trojan Classic 237. Everts, Tag: Hard Ten. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Trojan Classic 238. Rogers, Lance: Mutual Palmistry. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Trojan Classic 244. Rogers, Lance: Lord Of the Flies. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Trojan Classic 247. Tulane, Rick: Punk Spunk. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Trojan Classic 248. Stryker, Jack: The (Almost) Lone Ranger. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Trojan Classic 250. Rogers, Lance: Pulling A Boner. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Trojan Classic 254. White, Darryl: Old Queens Never Die. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Trojan Classic 267. Lawrence, Ross: AMTRAK-The Trickin' Trip. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Tudor Classic 102. Proferes, J.J: Cross Country Orgy. (Guild Press), 1971 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Unusual Sex Practices. Greenwood, M.D. (Genell Corporation), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Wildboys Collection 103. Boysen, Roger: Hot Hole Hustler. (Star), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Wildboys Collection 115. Wilson, George: Whipped and Creamed. (Star), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Wildboys Collection 117. Rossi, George: The Star's Boy Lovers. (Star), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Wildboys Collection 128. Thompson, Earl: Cum-On Cowhand. (Star), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Second Accretion
  - Ace 81651-7. Racina, Thom: Tomcat. (Ace Books), 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061157 9
  - Adam's Gay Readers 114. Hancock, Bob: Horny Stud Memories. (Surey), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Adam's Gay Reader 116. Van Damm, Dirk: Rub A Big Stud. (Surey), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Adam's Gay Reader 131. Martin, Andrew: Teen D.J.. (Star Distributors), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Adonis Classic 183. Lowe, F.W: Reform School Stud. (Greenleaf Classics), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ballantine Nonfiction 27577. Lloyd, Robin: For Money or Love, Boy Prostitution in America. (Ballantine), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ballantine Mystery 33167. Aldyne, Nathan: Canary. (Ballantine), 1986 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Blue Boy Library 113. Sawyer, Leo: Blind Windows. (Numbers), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Blue Boy Library 80056. Caldwell, Clay: Asphalt Cowboy. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Blue Boy Library 80069. Savage, Lon: Big Red. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Charter Fiction 74955-0. Coriolan, John: A Sand Fortress. (Universal), 1968 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Combat Books 107. Anonymous: Bound Captive. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Combat Books 108. Anonymous: Top Marine. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Combat Books 114. Anonymous: Big Black Sergeant. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Combat Books 123. Anonymous: Orgy Marines. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Combat Books 127. Anonymous: Boys At Sea. (Star Distributors), 1984 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Corgi Books. Jackson, Neville: No End To the Way. (Corgi), 1965 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Driveshaft Library 113. Baxter, Don: Island Meat. (Arena), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Driveshaft Library 114. Hayes, Adam: Greek Summer. (Arena), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Driveshaft Library 115. Richards, Mark: G.I. Jock. (Arena), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Driveshaft Library 117. Mason, Doug: Pumping Jocks. (Arena), 1982 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Driveshaft Library 118. Chadwick, Stu: Making the Team. (Arena), 1983 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Driveshaft Library 122. Chadwick, Stu: Brother to Brother. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061158 7
  - Driveshaft Library 124. Woodward, Mike: Bothers All the Way. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Driveshaft Library 125. Richards, Mark: Jock On the Road. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Driveshaft Library 127. Baxter, Don: Stud For Hire. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Driveshaft Library 128. Anderson, John: Brothers. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Driveshaft Library 130. Mason, Doug: Humpin' Jock. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Driveshaft Library 131. Baxter, Don: Skydiving Buddies. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Driveshaft Library 132. Woodward, Mike: United Studs. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Driveshaft Library 133. Baxter, Don: Tight End. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Driveshaft Library 136. Hayes, Adam: Plowboy. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Driveshaft Library 137. Mason, Doug: Hard At Work. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Driveshaft Library 138. Anderson, John: Hung Up On Peter. (Arena), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Flare Original Novel 82990. Ecker, B.A.: Independence Day. (Avon), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Finland Books 30. Anonymous: Raped Jocks. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Finland Books 37. Anonymous: Chained Gang. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Finland Books 38. Anonymous: Gym Dominators. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Finland Books 39. Anonymous: Cycle Studs. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Finland Books 45. Anonymous: Jock Strap. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Finland Books 48. Anonymous: Bike Boy. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Finland Books 53. Anonymous: Boy Trucker. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Finland Books 54. Anonymous: Brother Lover. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Finland Books 56. Anonymous: Cell Block 69.. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Finland Books 61. Anonymous: Loving Roommates. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Finland Books 71. Anonymous: Boys In Boot Camp. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Gay Incest 129. Anonymous: Dad's Champion Stud. (Star Distributors), 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061159 5
  - Gay Times Book Club 42. Anonymous: Sadist Soldiers. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Gay Times Book Club 43. Anonymous: Bad Ass Biker. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Gay Times Book Club 44. Anonymous: Lumberjack. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Gay Times Book Club 52. Anonymous: Come Hungry Cruiser. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Gay Times Book Club 53. Anonymous: Muscle Master. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Gay Times Book Club 61. Anonymous: Coming Out. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Gay Times Book Club 63. Anonymous: Best Buddy. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Gay Times Book Club 75. Anonymous: Initiation Night. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Gay Times Books Club 76. Anonymous: Punk Hustler. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Gay Times Book Club 79. Anonymous: Black Punk Hustler. (Star Distributors), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Gay Times Book Club 80. Anonymous: Marine Chicken. (Star Distributors), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69116. Howard, Chuck: Locker Room Lads. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69133. West, Samuel: Cream of Chicken. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69134. Hammer, Rod: The Male-Man's Bag. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69143. West, Samuel: Bathroom Buddies. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69245. Bennett, P.H.: Squaw Man. (Surrey House), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69467. Graeme, Roland: Damien II: The Youth. (Surrey House), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69468. Hartley, Jon: Carny Tricks. (Surrey House), 1983 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69471. Hartley, Jon: Call On Me. (Surrey House), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69472. Scott, D.A: Freshman Initiation. (Surrey Books), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Macho Books 6. Anonymous: The Tormentors. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061160 3
  - Macho Books 7. Anonymous: Prison Slave. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Macho Books 9. Anonymous: Big Rig Brutes. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Macho Books 12. Anonymous: Muscle Brutes. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Macho Books 15. Anonymous: Dorm Boys. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Manhard 459. Duncan, James: Fresh Young Buns. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Manpower 101. Carter, Matt: Locker Room Stud. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Manpower 104. Howard, Carlton: Team Hunk. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Manpower 107. Fields, Bruce: Longing For Peter. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Manpower 110. Howard, Carlton: Ass Trucker. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Midwood Books 60648. Greene, Jay: Nino. (Midwood), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Pinnacle Book 41-707-1. Caffey, John: The Coming Out Party. (Pinnacle), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Power Force Series 101. Dayton, Gary: Gary's Gay Odyssey. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Power Force Series 102. Stone, Mitch: Under Cover Gays. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Power Force Series 104. Sampson, David: Eager Hot Butt. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Power Force Series 108. Sampson, David: Hot Houseboy. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Power Force Series 109. Maston, Raymond: Hunky Cruiser. (Arena Publications), 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Rough Trade 511. Anonymous: Sailor's Liberty. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Rough Trade 512. Anonymous: Leather Knights. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Rough Trade 519. Anonymous: Backwood Bruisers. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Rough Trade 520. Anonymous: Iron Man. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Rough Trade 521. Anonymous: Chain Gang Chicken. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061161 1
  - Rough Trade 524. Anonymous: Brute Woodsman. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Rough Trade 526. Anonymous: Rodeo Stud. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Rough Trade 537. Anonymous: Muscle Men. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Rough Trade 538. Anonymous: Grease Monkey. (Star Distributors), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Rough Trade 542. Anonymous: Muscle Beach Brutes. (Star Distributors), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Signet 451-E7425. Hamilton, Wallace: Coming Out. (Signet), 1977 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Signet Vista 451-AE11898-7. Snyder, Anne: Counter Play. (Signet), 1981 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Spartacus Books 103. Shun, Erik: Chicken Farm. (Spartacus), 1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Special Publication. Anonymous: The Male Brothel [Fully Illustrated],. (s.l.), undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Surey Stud Series 23. Griffon, David: High-Ball Trucker. (Surey), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Surey Stud Series 24. Griffon, David: Ass Trucker. (Surey), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Surey Stud Series 132. Hartley, Jon: Backroom Piece. (Surey), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Trojan Classic 251. Tulane, Rick: Teen Cream. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Trojan Classic 259. Tulane, Rick: Stud Starch. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Untitled Series. Andrews, Teryl: Pageboys. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Untitled Series. Angel, W.D: Ten Bad Boys. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Untitled Series. Carter, Floyd: One A Night. (101 Enterprises), 1967 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Third Accretion
  - Adult Books 432. Brown, L.J: The Queens Are In the Parlor. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061200 7
  - All Star Books 46. Barnes, Gregory: Homo Alley. (All Star), 1965 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Almont House 125. West, Clarence: The Young Hawks. (Utopia Publications), 1974 (Box 39, Folder 3)